[{"answer": "No no no, behind it", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "That's right, I have a phone in here", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " All yours", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Shut up", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm not a baby, you're the baby", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You wanna get out of my face", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Morning. I just uh, came by to pick up my mail.  Where's the mail", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You don't keep it over here on this table any more", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh it's uh, over there on the table", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, my friend likes to keep it over there", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well I do, but uh, my friend makes them this way and, well they're pretty darn good", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "See ya.", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Alright, so what's it about", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well I like both eggs equally", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Eggs. Who's eggs do you like better, his or mine, huh", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh come on. Nobody likes two different kinds of eggs equally. You like one better than the other and I wanna know which", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Ow, ow, OK. Alright, alright, Mon, Mon, you've gone ultrasonic again, alright", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Why, why, why can't you stand me being here? I don't, I, we're just, ya know, we're just havin' fun", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Why, why, why can't you stand me being here? I don't, I, we're just, ya know, we're just havin' fun", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yeah, c'mon I mean I though, you know, I thought we're just foolin' around. Like when, uh, when we were kids", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah, c'mon I mean I though, you know, I thought we're just foolin' around. Like when, uh, when we were kids", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You hated me when we were kids", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Yeah ", "docId": "217emi.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You don't like that show", "qsentId": 26}]